PANDORA: BENEATH THE PARADISE
باندورا: بينية الجنة
EPISODE 7
الحلقة 7
[Seondeok] The night of Hong Yura's death,
[Seondeok] ليلة وفاة هونغ يورا ،
what were you doing at the dock near the lake, Mr. Pyo,
ماذا كنت تفعل في قفص الاتهام بالقرب من البحيرة ، سيد بيو ،
wearing a black raincoat?
يرتدي معطف واق من المطر أسود؟
Looks like you're willing to talk, judging by the look on your face.
يبدو أنك على استعداد للتحدث ، بناءً على مظهر وجهك.
Hatch is currently worth over 20 trillion won.
تبلغ قيمة هاتش حاليًا أكثر من 20 تريليون وون.
Why don't you hand Hatch over to me?
لماذا لا تسلمني هاتش؟
Hand Hatch over…
تسليم هاتش ...
to you?
لك؟
You'll need to set up a blind trust for your stocks
ستحتاج إلى إنشاء ثقة عمياء للأسهم الخاصة بك
before you enter the Blue House anyway.
قبل أن تدخل البيت الأزرق على أي حال.
What if I were the independent trustee?
ماذا لو كنت الوصي المستقل؟
A presidential term is fleeting, you know.
فترة الرئاسة عابرة ، كما تعلم.
I'll return half of it to you upon your return to civilian life.
سأعيد لك نصفها عند عودتك إلى الحياة المدنية.
How does that sound?
كيف يبدو هذا؟
You were painting a bigger picture than I'd assumed.
كنت ترسم صورة أكبر مما توقعت.
[Seondeok laughs]
[يضحك Seondeok]
Well, I'll admit, you're a masterful artist yourself.
حسنًا ، سأعترف ، أنت نفسك فنانة بارعة.
Greasing Uhm's fist to get him to make it seem like Chairman Jang is behind it all.
تشحيم قبضة Uhm لجعله يبدو وكأن الرئيس Jang وراء كل ذلك.
Now that's a masterpiece.
الآن هذه تحفة.
Clearly, you're no ordinary man.
من الواضح أنك لست رجلاً عاديًا.
You almost had me fooled, sir.
لقد كادت أن تخدعني يا سيدي.
I'm afraid I don't know what you mean.
أخشى أنني لا أعرف ما تعنيه.
I suppose you leave me no choice but to speak about your wife.
أفترض أنك لا تترك لي أي خيار سوى التحدث عن زوجتك.
Hong Taera.
هونغ تايرا.
I personally prefer calling her No. 50.
أنا شخصياً أفضل الاتصال بها برقم 50.
No. 50 is the assassin that Ko Haesoo is madly intent on finding, no?
رقم 50 هو القاتل الذي ينوي كو هايسو البحث عنه بجنون ، أليس كذلك؟
And the man who turned No. 50 into Hong Taera was you, yes?
والرجل الذي حول رقم 50 إلى Hong Taera هو أنت ، أليس كذلك؟
I gather you got rid of Hong Yura because she found out the truth.
أعلم أنك تخلصت من هونغ يورا لأنها اكتشفت الحقيقة.
At last, the puzzle has been solved.
أخيرًا ، تم حل اللغز.
I suppose this very meeting we're having
أفترض أن هذا الاجتماع بالذات نجريه
was probably a part of the plan, wasn't it?
ربما كان جزءًا من الخطة ، أليس كذلك؟
Is Taera aware of the things you're saying to me?
هل تيرا على علم بالأشياء التي تقولها لي؟
Why would I run my mouth without my partner's consent?
لماذا أدير فمي دون موافقة شريكي؟
[sighs]
[تنهدات]
Whatever you're planning, I want to be a part of it,
مهما كان ما تخطط له ، أريد أن أكون جزءًا منه ،
as an official partner of yours.
كشريك رسمي لك.
Pinning everything on Chairman Jang to take over Kumjo,
تثبيت كل شيء على الرئيس جانغ لتولي Kumjo ،
becoming the president to take over this country,
يصبح الرئيس لتولي هذا البلد ،
I'm all for it.
انا كلى لها.
[Seondeok laughs]
[يضحك Seondeok]
But, first, why don't you give Mr. Jo back to me?
لكن ، أولاً ، لماذا لا تعيد السيد جو لي؟
You wasted your time with a stray because I'd let my boy loose.
لقد أهدرت وقتك مع ضال لأنني تركت ولدي يضيع.
I'll make sure this never happens again.
سوف أتأكد من أن هذا لن يحدث مرة أخرى.
Your turn to show your cards.
دورك لإظهار البطاقات الخاصة بك.
Who did you plant to keep tabs on me?
من الذي زرعته ليراقبني؟
Who's the brave soul who dared to tread on my turf…
من هي الروح الشجاعة التي تجرأت على أن تخطو على أرضي ...
and take these photos of me?
وأخذ هذه الصور لي؟
[No. 105 screams]
[لا.  105 صرخات]
It's time you give up on Haesoo.
حان الوقت للتخلي عن Haesoo.
Over my dead body.
على جثتي.
[No. 105 grunting]
[لا.  105 الشخير]
[No. 50 gasps]
[لا.  50 شهقة]
It was you?
لقد كنت أنت؟
[No. 105 breathes shakily]
[لا.  105 يتنفس مرتعش]
[No. 50] Thank you
[لا.  50] شكرا لك
for surviving.
من أجل البقاء.
[Seondeok] Remember, you can't kill No. 50 yet.
[Seondeok] تذكر ، لا يمكنك قتل رقم 50 بعد.
[No. 50 gasps]
[لا.  50 شهقة]
Mr. Park?
السيد بارك؟
[Haesoo screams]
[صرخات هيسو]
She must be here. Search thoroughly!
يجب أن تكون هنا.  ابحث بدقة!
[bodyguards] Yes, sir!
[حراس شخصيون] نعم سيدي!
[footsteps]
[خطوات]
[Dojin] Haesoo! Ko Haesoo!
[دوجين] هايسو!  أو Haesoo!
Haesoo!
يا!
- Ko Haesoo! - [Haesoo] Dojin, over here!
- كو هيسو! - [هيسو] دوجين ، هنا!
We need to get him to a hospital.
نحن بحاجة إلى نقله إلى المستشفى.
HANWOOL MENTAL HOSPITAL
مستشفى حنوول العقلي
[Seondeok humming]
[همهمة Seondeok]
[Seondeok grunts]
[همهمات Seondeok]
Why didn't you tell me Hajun was alive?
لماذا لم تخبرني أن هاجون كان على قيد الحياة؟
You wanted to see how long it would take me to recognize him?
كنت تريد أن ترى كم من الوقت سيستغرق مني للتعرف عليه؟
Were you amused?
هل كنت مستمتعا؟
Mother Director, are you okay?
الأم المديرة ، هل أنت بخير؟
Mother Director?
أم مديرة؟
No. 105 was only supposed to scare you, but it seems he slipped up this time.
رقم 105 كان من المفترض أن يخيفك فقط ، لكن يبدو أنه انزلق هذه المرة.
Of course.
بالطبع.
His heartless sister abandoned him as a child.
أخته التي لا قلب لها تخلت عنه عندما كان طفلا.
No wonder he lost his temper.
لا عجب أنه فقد أعصابه.
[Seondeok] Tsk, tsk, tsk.
[Seondeok] تسك ، تسك ، تسك.
Bring her in.
أحضرها.
[door opens, closes]
[الباب يفتح ، يغلق]
It is done.
تم.
Leave us.
اتركنا.
She tried to kill you, Mother.
حاولت قتلك يا أمي.
Why should I worry when I have you? I'll be fine.
لماذا يجب أن أقلق عندما يكون عندي؟  سأكون بخير.
[door opens, closes]
[الباب يفتح ، يغلق]
You shouldn't resent me.
لا يجب أن تستاء مني.
The accident had crushed his leg,
لقد أصاب الحادث ساقه ،
but I was the one who treated him and took him under my wing.
لكنني كنت من عالجته وأخذته تحت جناحي.
The least you can do is thank me.
أقل ما يمكنك فعله هو شكري.
You tried to get him killed.
لقد حاولت قتله.
Mr. Jo ran him over with the car, not me.
دهسه السيد جو بالسيارة ، وليس أنا.
But he lost one of his eyes because of you.
لكنه فقد إحدى عينيه بسببك.
Doesn't that make us even?
ألا يجعلنا ذلك متساويين؟
Whoa, whoa.
قف ، قف.
No need to sharpen the blade.
لا حاجة لشحذ النصل.
I have no intention of revealing your true identity.
ليس لدي أي نية للكشف عن هويتك الحقيقية.
We're in the same boat now.
نحن الآن في نفس القارب.
I'd love for you to become the first lady.
أحب أن تصبح السيدة الأولى.
I sincerely do.
أنا بصدق أفعل.
Drop the bullshit.
أسقط الهراء.
Don't you want to protect your brother?
ألا تريد حماية أخيك؟
If the truth of that day 15 years ago comes out,
إذا ظهرت حقيقة ذلك اليوم قبل 15 عامًا ،
you must know your brother will be in grave danger.
يجب أن تعلم أن أخيك سيكون في خطر شديد.
[Seondeok sighs]
[يتنهد Seondeok]
We'd be remiss if you stay out too late.
سنكون مقصرين إذا بقيت بالخارج بعد فوات الأوان.
We must be precious about our future first lady.
يجب أن نكون ثمينين بشأن مستقبل السيدة الأولى.
[Seondeok] No. 105.
[Seondeok] رقم 105.
Yes, Mother Director.
نعم مديرة الأم.
[Seondeok] Think carefully
[Seondeok] فكر جيدًا
about how to best protect No. 105.
حول أفضل طريقة لحماية رقم 105.
Take Ms. Hong home.
خذ السيدة هونغ المنزل.
- Safely. - Yes, ma'am.
- بأمان.  - نعم، سيدتي.
[Seondeok] If the truth of that day 15 years ago comes out,
[Seondeok] إذا ظهرت حقيقة ذلك اليوم قبل 15 عامًا ،
you must know your brother will be in grave danger.
يجب أن تعلم أن أخيك سيكون في خطر شديد.
[siren wailing]
[نحيب صفارات الانذار]
I saw
لقد رأيت
Taera back there.
Taera مرة أخرى هناك.
Why would she be there?
لماذا ستكون هناك؟
If Director Kim did this to Mr. Park
إذا كان المدير كيم فعل هذا للسيد بارك
and Taera was there,
وكان تيرا هناك ،
it may prove you right.
قد يثبت أنك على حق.
Whatever the case,
مهما كانت الحالة،
I think Taera is somehow associated with your father's assassination.
أعتقد أن تيرا مرتبطة بطريقة ما باغتيال والدك.
[Haesoo sighs]
[يتنهد هيسو]
Sorry, honey.
اسف حبيبتي.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
[No. 105] Have a good night, ma'am.
[لا.  105] أتمنى لك ليلة سعيدة يا سيدتي.
Hey…
يا…
I've nothing to say. Neither should you, ma'am.
ليس لدي ما أقوله.  ولا يجب عليك يا سيدتي.
[No. 50] Hajun.
[حسنًا.  50] أشم.
I'm sorry, I…
انا اسف ...
I really thought you were dead.
اعتقدت حقا أنك ميت.
After you fell off my bike,
بعد أن سقطت من دراجتي ،
I fell off the cliff. Then I lost my memory.
لقد سقطت من الجرف.  ثم فقدت ذاكرتي.
Had I known you were at Hanwool, I would've gotten you out of there.
لو كنت أعرف أنك في Hanwool ، لكنت أخرجتك من هناك.
I never would've left you with her.
لم أكن لأتركك معها أبدًا.
You have to cut ties with her. You know what she's like.
عليك قطع العلاقات معها.  أنت تعرف ما هي عليه.
You need to leave her now. I'll find a safe place--
عليك أن تتركها الآن.  سأجد مكانًا آمنًا--
Talk about Mother Director like that one more time,
تحدث عن الأم المديرة هكذا مرة أخرى ،
believe me,
ثق بي،
I will kill you.
سأقتلك.
[crying]
[بكاء]
[No. 50] Let's get acquainted slowly.
[لا.  50] دعنا نتعرف ببطء.
Pilseung.
بيلسونغ.
No. You shouldn't drive in that state.
لا ، لا يجب أن تقود في تلك الحالة.
I told you to watch Jiu constantly.
قلت لك أن تشاهد جيو باستمرار.
If anything happens to her…
إذا حدث لها أي شيء ...
[tires squeal]
[صرير الإطارات]
[No. 50] You must have resented me so much,
[لا.  50] لا بد أنك استاءتني كثيرًا ،
waiting for me at that hellish place.
ينتظرني في ذلك المكان الجهنمية.
You must have wanted to kill me every day.
لابد أنك أردت قتلي كل يوم.
Hajun,
أنا أشم
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
I-- I really didn't know.
أنا - لم أكن أعرف حقًا.
No!
لا!
Sis!
أختي!
Where's my sister? Hagyeong!
اين اختي  هاغيونغ!
Where is my sister?
أين أختي؟
How many times do I have to tell you she's gone?
كم مرة يجب أن أخبرك أنها رحلت؟
Still can't forget your shitty sister?
ما زلت لا تستطيع أن تنسى أختك القذرة؟
She told me we would live together.
أخبرتني أننا سنعيش معًا.
She said she'd never leave me again!
قالت إنها لن تتركني مرة أخرى!
It's been months since you had surgery,
لقد مرت شهور منذ أن أجريت لك الجراحة ،
and your sister never once showed up!
وأختك لم تحضر مرة واحدة!
No! She's coming. She's coming for me--
لا!  هي قادمه.  إنها قادمة من أجلي--
Wrong. She's never coming back.
خطأ.  انها لن تعود ابدا.
The only person you have left to trust…
الشخص الوحيد المتبقي لك لتثق به ...
is me.
هو انا.
Mother Director is all you have now, No. 105.
الأم المخرجة هي كل ما لديك الآن ، رقم 105.
Your Mother Director.
مديرة والدتك.
No. 105…
رقم 105 ...
I'm all you have.
انا كل ما عندك.
[pills rattle]
[خشخشة حبوب]
[sighs]
[تنهدات]
[Jaehyun] Who did you plant to keep tabs on me?
[Jaehyun] من الذي زرعته ليراقبني؟
Who's the brave soul who dared to tread on my turf…
من هي الروح الشجاعة التي تجرأت على أن تخطو على أرضي ...
and take these photos of me?
وأخذ هذه الصور لي؟
I get my answer before you get yours, Mr. Pyo!
أحصل على إجابتي قبل أن تحصل على إجابتك ، سيد بيو!
Something wrong?
هل هناك خطب ما ؟
No, it's nothing.
لا لا شيء.
Were you crying?
كنت تبكي؟
Don't be silly.
لا تكن سخيفا.
I couldn't reach you earlier.
لم أستطع الوصول إليك في وقت سابق.
Where'd you go? I was worried.
الى أبن تريد الذهاب؟  كنت قلقا.
I went out for some air.
خرجت لبعض الهواء.
I have security anyway.
لدي أمن على أي حال.
I'll go check on Jiu.
سأذهب للتحقق من Jiu.
Don't fret over Haesoo.
لا تقلق من Haesoo.
You don't have to be apologetic to Dojin either.
ليس عليك أن تعتذر لـ Dojin أيضًا.
Right, now let's think about us.
حسنًا ، الآن دعنا نفكر فينا.
"Us"?
"نحن"؟
You, me, and Jiu.
أنت وأنا وجيو.
The most precious people in my life.
اغلى الناس في حياتي.
My family is all I need.
عائلتي هي كل ما احتاجه.
Don't you feel the same?
ألا تشعر بالمثل؟
Haesoo and Dojin are important people in our lives too.
Haesoo و Dojin شخصان مهمان في حياتنا أيضًا.
Not anymore.
ليس بعد الآن.
By the way, we found office space for the campaign team.
بالمناسبة ، وجدنا مساحة مكتبية لفريق الحملة.
I know it hasn't been easy.
أعلم أن الأمر لم يكن سهلاً.
And there seems to be a problem with the town house security.
ويبدو أن هناك مشكلة في أمن منزل المدينة.
I might replace all staff and security personnel.
قد أستبدل جميع الموظفين وأفراد الأمن.
Even Pilseung?
حتى بيلسونغ؟
Mmm.
ممم.
Can we keep him around?
هل يمكننا إبقائه في الجوار؟
Jiu gets along with him well, and I feel comfortable with him too.
جيو تتفق معه بشكل جيد ، وأنا أشعر بالراحة معه أيضًا.
I don't want to have to get used to someone new.
لا أريد التعود على شخص جديد.
If you have a problem with him,
إذا كانت لديك مشكلة معه ،
I'd prefer if we don't replace him.
أنا أفضل إذا لم نستبدله.
[chuckles]
[ضحكات خافتة]
If that's what you want.
اذا كان هذا ما تريده.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Is Director Koo still in there?
هل المخرج كو لا يزال هناك؟
He pulled an all-nighter.
لقد سهر طوال الليل.
[Yang] Director Koo.
[يانغ] المخرج كو.
What? What's going on?
ماذا؟  ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Have you begun a new research project? Anything I can help with?
هل بدأت مشروع بحث جديد؟  هل من شيء يمكنني المساعدة به؟
Nope. Don't worry about that.
لا.  لا تقلق بشأن ذلك.
Right. Beware that the special research lab is off-limits for the time being.
يمين.  احذر من أن مختبر الأبحاث الخاص محظور في الوقت الحالي.
If you dare go in,
إذا كنت تجرؤ على الدخول ،
you're dead.
انت ميت.
- Yes, sir. - [scientist] Understood.
- نعم سيدي.  - [عالم] مفهوم.
Going somewhere?
الذهاب الى مكان ما؟
Thought I'd take some food to Sungchan.
اعتقدت أنني سأأخذ بعض الطعام إلى Sungchan.
He's been looking out of sorts after Yura's incident.
لقد كان يبحث من نوع ما بعد حادثة يورا.
I should've checked up on him. Thank you, honey.
كان يجب أن أفحصه.  اشكرك حبيبتى.
- You're coming to the office opening? - We'll see.
- أنت قادم إلى افتتاح المكتب؟  - سوف نرى.
- Be sure to pack everything. - [assistant] Yes, sir.
- تأكد من حزم كل شيء.  - [المساعد] نعم سيدي.
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخلوي]
Yeah, it's me.
نعم انه انا.
Director Koo banned us from entering the special lab,
منعنا المخرج كو من دخول المختبر الخاص ،
so I can't confirm the subject's status. Apologies, sir.
لذلك لا يمكنني تأكيد حالة الموضوع.  معذرة يا سيدي.
Do anything you can to find out
افعل أي شيء لتكتشفه
if the smart patch works on humans and if the Neural Input Program succeeded.
إذا كان التصحيح الذكي يعمل على البشر وإذا نجح برنامج الإدخال العصبي.
Find out, no matter what, okay?
اكتشف ، مهما كان الأمر ، حسنًا؟
[Jaehyun] If Kyojin is awake,
[جيهيون] إذا كان كيوجين مستيقظًا ،
that can only mean Sungchan has the flash drive.
هذا يمكن أن يعني فقط أن Sungchan لديه محرك أقراص فلاش.
[No. 50] Is Kyojin awake?
[رقم 50] هل كيوجين مستيقظ؟
He's conscious now, but communicating is another issue.
إنه واع الآن ، لكن التواصل موضوع آخر.
The input process might take longer, since he's been comatose for so long.
قد تستغرق عملية الإدخال وقتًا أطول ، لأنه كان في غيبوبة لفترة طويلة.
Does Jaehyun know?
هل يعلم جيهيون؟
No, but he'll probably do anything to find out.
لا ، لكنه على الأرجح سيفعل أي شيء لمعرفة ذلك.
Are you sure Jaehyun had a hand in Kyojin's accident?
هل أنت متأكد من أن جيهيون كان له دور في حادث كيوجين؟
Only Kyojin will know for sure.
فقط كيوجين سيعرف بالتأكيد.
If Jaehyun was behind the accident, why would he want Kyojin to wake up?
إذا كان Jaehyun وراء الحادث ، فلماذا يريد Kyojin أن يستيقظ؟
It would do him no good.
لن يفيده ذلك.
I can't figure that out either.
لا يمكنني معرفة ذلك أيضًا.
When will you tell Dojin?
متى ستخبر دوجين؟
Make one careless move, and Jaehyun will suspect me.
قم بحركة واحدة مهملة ، وسوف يشك بي جيهيون.
For now, we'll have to wait until the Neural Input Program is done.
في الوقت الحالي ، سيتعين علينا الانتظار حتى يتم الانتهاء من برنامج الإدخال العصبي.
Sungchan,
سونغشان ،
I need your help.
انا بحاجة الى مساعدتكم.
KOREA FOR THE WORLD TO SEE WE STAND WITH PYO JAEHYUN
كوريا للعالم أن يرى أننا نقف مع PYO JAEHYUN
[Jaehyun] This is only the beginning.
- هذه فقط البداية.
The election cycle starts tomorrow,
تبدأ الدورة الانتخابية غدًا ،
so let's prove our potential.
لذلك دعونا نثبت إمكاناتنا.
"Korea for the world to see. We stand with Pyo Jaehyun."
"كوريا ليراها العالم. نحن نقف مع بيو جيهيون."
[all] Korea for the world to see. We stand with Pyo Jaehyun!
[كل] كوريا ليراها العالم.  نحن نقف مع بيو جيهيون!
[applause]
[تصفيق]
[No. 50] Congratulations.
[لا.  50] مبروك.
Honey.
عسل.
Welcome, Ms. Hong. Oh, thank you.
مرحباً ، السيدة هونغ.  اوه شكرا لك.
You all must be exhausted.
يجب أن تكونوا مرهقين.
- Help him as much as you can. - Of course.
- ساعده بقدر ما تستطيع.  - بالطبع.
Also, this isn't much, but take the staff out for a nice meal.
أيضًا ، هذا ليس كثيرًا ، لكن اصطحب الموظفين لتناول وجبة لطيفة.
We appreciate it. Thank you!
نحن نقدر ذلك.  شكرًا لك!
Yay!
ياي!
Well, that uplifted the mood.
حسنًا ، لقد رفع هذا المزاج.
Let me know if you need anything.
اخبرني اذا احتجت شيئا.
I will. Thank you, Taera.
أنا سوف.  شكرا لك تيرا.
Pardon me, sir. You must leave now for the luncheon.
عفوا سيدي.  يجب أن تغادر الآن لتناول الغداء.
Go ahead, honey.
هيا عزيزتي.
Is it okay if I look around a little?
هل لا بأس إذا نظرت حولي قليلاً؟
Well, of course. Look around all you want.
حسنا بالطبع.  انظر حولك كل ما تريد.
- Shall we go? - Yes, sir. This way.
- هل نذهب؟  - نعم سيدي.  من هنا.
PYO JAEHYUN WILL DO IT! INDEPENDENT, PYO JAEHYUN
سوف تفعلها PYO JAEHYUN!  مستقل ، PYO JAEHYUN
I have control of the cameras. Let's begin.
لدي السيطرة على الكاميرات.  هيا نبدأ.
The wiretap is planted under the desk.
تم زرع جهاز التنصت تحت المكتب.
As for the camera…
بالنسبة للكاميرا ...
One moment.
لحظة واحدة.
Can you see me?
هل بإمكانك رؤيتي؟
[Sungchan] Clear as day.
[Sungchan] واضح كالنوم.
I've disabled the sensors from catching any signals.
لقد عطلت أجهزة الاستشعار عن التقاط أي إشارات.
And now we hack
وها نحن الآن نتسلل
Jaehyun's car system.
نظام سيارة Jaehyun.
Okay.
تمام.
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخلوي]
[Seondeok] You only need to bring Jo out, Mr. Pyo.
[Seondeok] ما عليك سوى إخراج جو ، سيد بيو.
I'll do the rest.
سأفعل الباقي.
[Kummo] I knew you'd call, Mr. Pyo.
[كومو] كنت أعرف أنك ستتصلين ، سيد بيو.
Let's meet today,
دعونا نجتمع اليوم،
same place.
نفس المكان.
[Dojin chuckles]
[ضحكات خافتة دوجين]
What time is it?
أي ساعة؟
Sleep some more. You barely got any.
نم أكثر.  بالكاد حصلت على أي منها.
No, I need to call the jeweler.
لا ، أنا بحاجة للاتصال بالصائغ.
I called them already.
اتصلت بهم بالفعل.
Thank you, Dojin.
شكرا لك دوجين.
I don't deserve your gratitude yet.
أنا لا أستحق امتنانك بعد.
First, we catch the real killer and the mastermind.
أولاً ، نقبض على القاتل الحقيقي والعقل المدبر.
Then-- Then let's pay our respects to your parents.
ثم - إذن فلنقدم احترامنا لوالديك.
My mom,
أمي،
even through all the accusations,
حتى من خلال كل الاتهامات ،
she never once complained to me.
لم تشكو لي مرة واحدة.
But I…
لكن أنا…
I was so scared she might have had something to do with it.
كنت خائفة جدًا من أن يكون لها علاقة بها.
So I avoided her.
لذلك تجنبتها.
If it's because of me…
إذا كان ذلك بسببي ...
If my treatment of her drove her to suicide,
إذا دفعتها معاملتي لها إلى الانتحار ،
how can I live with that, Dojin?
كيف يمكنني العيش مع ذلك دوجين؟
It's not your fault.
انها ليست غلطتك.
She wouldn't have thought of you that way, Haesoo. Never.
لم تكن تفكر فيك بهذه الطريقة يا هيسو.  أبداً.
Your parents would know better than anyone about your efforts to get to the truth.
سيعرف والداك أكثر من أي شخص آخر عن جهودك للوصول إلى الحقيقة.
So, let's uncover this together and see who's behind all this.
لذا ، دعونا نكشف النقاب عن هذا معًا ونرى من وراء كل هذا.
Hey, Mr. Park. How are you feeling?
مرحبًا ، السيد بارك.  كيف تشعر؟
Have you seen the news?
هل رأيت الأخبار؟
INDEPENDENT CANDIDATE PYO'S WIFE FALSIFIED IDENTITY?
هل تم تزوير هوية زوجة المرشح المستقل بيو؟
The Korean Democratic Party is running with your story about Hong Taera.
يعمل الحزب الديمقراطي الكوري مع قصتك عن Hong Taera.
Han Kyungrok did that?
فعل هان كيونغروك ذلك؟
How is Chairman Jang doing? He's a hard man to meet these days.
كيف حال الرئيس جانغ؟  إنه رجل يصعب مقابلته هذه الأيام.
NO. 1, HAN KYUNGROK
رقم 1 ، هان كينجروك
I've been a nuisance to him recently. I'm sure I'm not making it easier for him.
لقد كنت مصدر إزعاج له مؤخرًا.  أنا متأكد من أنني لا أجعل الأمر أسهل بالنسبة له.
[laughs] Your special with Candidate Pyo sure was quite entertaining.
[يضحك] كان عرضك الخاص مع المرشح بيو مسليًا للغاية بالتأكيد.
I doubt you caused such a commotion based purely on conjecture.
أشك في أنك تسببت في مثل هذه الضجة المبنية فقط على التخمين.
There is something, huh?
هناك شيء ما ، أليس كذلك؟
The article on Hong's fake identity was also enjoyable.
المقال عن هوية هونغ المزيفة كان ممتعًا أيضًا.
It was almost identical to my findings.
كانت مطابقة تقريبًا لنتائجي.
I know someone who corroborated the truth.
أعرف شخصًا أكد الحقيقة.
You mean there's a witness?
تقصد ان هناك شاهد؟
Yes. The real Hong Taera's friend.
نعم.  الصديق الحقيقي لـ Hong Taera.
But I can't seem to reach her.
لكن يبدو أنني لا أستطيع الوصول إليها.
I've sent someone over to find her.
لقد أرسلت شخصًا ما ليجدها.
Mr. Pyo… Wow.
السيد بيو ... واو.
He sure has a knack for surprises.
من المؤكد أنه لديه موهبة المفاجآت.
We have some information ourselves.
لدينا بعض المعلومات بأنفسنا.
It's about Mr. Pyo's late mother.
إنه عن والدة السيد بيو الراحلة.
She was quite problematic.
كانت إشكالية للغاية.
Not that we're complaining.
لا يعني ذلك أننا نشكو.
CANDIDATE NO. 1 HAN KYUNGROK
المرشح لا.  1 هان كينجروك
What's with the long face? What'd he say?
ما مع الوجه الطويل؟  ماذا قال؟
Have you, by any chance, heard anything about Jaehyun's parents?
هل سمعت بأي فرصة عن والدي جيهيون؟
I've never heard anything about his father,
لم أسمع أي شيء عن والده ،
but I know his mother passed away in a car crash.
لكنني أعلم أن والدته توفيت في حادث سيارة.
I heard she was a doctor.
سمعت أنها كانت طبيبة.
And how did you first meet Jaehyun?
وكيف قابلت جايهيون لأول مرة؟
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
- Damn bastard's not picking up. - Still no answer?
- اللعين اللقيط لا يلتقط.  - لا يزال هناك جواب؟
Game's starting soon.
ستبدأ اللعبة قريبًا.
Maybe he chickened out? Face it, you've lost.
ربما كان الدجاج خارج؟  واجه الأمر ، لقد خسرت.
Oh, that sh--
أوه ، هذا sh--
Man, can't anyone take his place?
يا رجل ، ألا يستطيع أحد أن يحل محله؟
[stranger] Can I jump in?
[غريب] هل يمكنني القفز؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm Pyo Jaehyun.
أنا بيو جيهيون.
- Pleasure. - Can you play ball?
- سرور.  - هل يمكنك لعب الكرة؟
- [spectator] It's in! - [spectator 2] Wow!
- [متفرج] إنه في!  - [متفرج 2] واو!
- [player] Shoot! - [all] Wow!
- [لاعب] أطلق النار!  - [الكل] نجاح باهر!
- [player 2] Good going, man! - [all] All right!
- [اللاعب 2] جيد يا رجل!  - [كل] حسنًا!
- [Dojin] Good game, man! - Wow!
- [Dojin] لعبة جيدة يا رجل!  - رائع!
You're pretty good.
انت جيدة جدا.
- What's your major? - Neural engineering. I transferred here.
- ما هو التخصص الخاص بك؟  - الهندسة العصبية.  لقد انتقلت هنا.
- And before? - Seoul University, College of Medicine.
- و قبل؟  - جامعة سيول ، كلية الطب.
No wonder I'd never seen you before.
لا عجب أنني لم أرك من قبل.
We know everyone who can play ball here.
نحن نعرف كل من يمكنه لعب الكرة هنا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
[Dojin] Drinks on me today! See you at the usual spot.
[دوجين] يشرب علي اليوم!  نراكم في المكان المعتاد.
Order anything you want!
اطلب أي شيء تريده!
[cheering]
[هتاف]
Come on. Let's go! It's a go from me!
تعال.  دعنا نذهب!  انها تذهب مني!
Well,
حسنًا،
instead of drinks, can you do me a favor?
بدلا من المشروبات هل تصنع لي معروفا؟
Introduce me to the club president.
قدمني لرئيس النادي.
My brother?
أخي؟
I transferred here because of Kyojin. I want to join his research team.
لقد انتقلت إلى هنا بسبب Kyojin.  أريد أن أنضم إلى فريق بحثه.
He transferred to KAIST because of Kyojin?
انتقل إلى KAIST بسبب Kyojin؟
What was he researching at the time?
ما الذي كان يبحث في ذلك الوقت؟
Some research about cranial nerves.
بعض الأبحاث حول الأعصاب القحفية.
He was quite popular back then too, and people were dying to meet him.
كان يتمتع بشعبية كبيرة في ذلك الوقت أيضًا ، وكان الناس يموتون لمقابلته.
He was the genius from a wealthy family.
كان عبقريا من عائلة ثرية.
A lot of people hid their true colors to get to know him through me,
أخفى الكثير من الناس ألوانهم الحقيقية للتعرف عليه من خلالي ،
but Jaehyun was straightforward.
لكن جيهيون كان صريحًا.
What about the friend who was supposed to play?
ماذا عن الصديق الذي كان من المفترض أن يلعب؟
There was an accident on his way here.
كان هناك حادث في طريقه إلى هنا.
His bicycle suddenly broke down.
دراجته تعطلت فجأة.
He even had to get surgery.
حتى أنه اضطر إلى إجراء عملية جراحية.
But Jaehyun suddenly appeared to take his spot.
لكن ظهر فجأة أن جاهيون أخذ مكانه.
Dojin, can you look into Jaehyun some more?
دوجين ، هل يمكنك النظر إلى Jaehyun أكثر؟
From when he was at SNU Medicine-- No, even before then.
منذ أن كان في SNU Medicine - لا ، حتى قبل ذلك.
Especially about his late mother.
خاصة عن والدته الراحلة.
[Younghwee] How is Kyojin doing?
[يونغوي] كيف حال كيوجين؟
[Jaehyun] We're operating the system, and it's going well.
- نحن نشغل النظام ، وهو يسير على ما يرام.
It won't be easy to recover after seven years, but don't worry.
لن يكون من السهل التعافي بعد سبع سنوات ، لكن لا تقلق.
Some may say this is a miracle, but not me.
قد يقول البعض أن هذه معجزة ، لكن ليس أنا.
My Kyojin is very strong.
Kyojin الخاص بي قوي جدًا.
He's going to walk again.
سوف يمشي مرة أخرى.
Of course. I know Kyojin will.
بالطبع.  أنا أعلم أن كيوجين سوف.
He has to.
عليه ان.
I'm planning to buy Kumjo stocks under Kyojin's name.
أخطط لشراء أسهم Kyojin تحت اسم Kyojin.
Great idea, Ms. Min.
فكرة عظيمة يا سيدة مين.
Kyojin should take over Kumjo, rightfully so.
يجب أن يتولى Kyojin مسؤولية Kumjo ، بحق.
My husband will find out in no time and try to rush Dojin's succession.
زوجي سوف يكتشف ذلك في أي وقت من الأوقات ويحاول الإسراع في خلافة دوجين.
We can't let that happen.
لا يمكننا أن ندع ذلك يحدث.
For Kyojin.
من أجل Kyojin.
I'll get going. The campaign team's dealing with a crisis.
سأذهب.  فريق الحملة يتعامل مع أزمة.
If I'm not careful, I may lose this game.
إذا لم أكن حريصًا ، فقد أخسر هذه اللعبة.
Not on my watch.
ليس في مناوبتي.
Can I help in any way?
هل يمكنني المساعدة بأي شكل من الأشكال؟
Whether it's campaign funds or anything, just say the word.
سواء كانت أموال الحملة أو أي شيء ، فقط قل الكلمة.
I have enough money, Ms. Min--
لدي ما يكفي من المال ، السيدة مين--
I know,
أنا أعرف،
but funds from your own company can look bad for you in politics.
لكن الأموال من شركتك الخاصة يمكن أن تبدو سيئة بالنسبة لك في السياسة.
I have some cash saved up.
لدي بعض النقود ادخرت.
[Sangbae] Here are Kumjo Group's financial statements
[Sangbae] فيما يلي البيانات المالية لمجموعة Kumjo
from the past five years.
من السنوات الخمس الماضية.
Starting tomorrow, we'll start visiting our subsidiaries.
ابتداءً من الغد ، سنبدأ في زيارة الشركات التابعة لنا.
Before your succession, you should introduce yourself first.
قبل خلافتك ، يجب أن تقدم نفسك أولاً.
Chairman Jang has planned your itinerary himself.
لقد خطط الرئيس جانغ لمسار رحلتك بنفسه.
Well, it looks like he'd always been prepared for my return to Kumjo.
حسنًا ، يبدو أنه كان دائمًا مستعدًا لعودتي إلى كومجو.
Everything is meant to fall into its rightful place.
كل شيء من المفترض أن يقع في مكانه الصحيح.
Please tell my father,
من فضلك قل لوالدي ،
now that I'm back at Kumjo,
الآن بعد أن عدت إلى Kumjo ،
he must keep his promise to help my wife.
يجب أن يفي بوعده بمساعدة زوجتي.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Also…
أيضًا…
can I ask for a personal favor?
هل يمكنني طلب خدمة شخصية؟
I'd appreciate it if Father didn't know.
سأكون ممتنًا لو لم يعلم أبي.
From hospital records
من سجلات المستشفى
to proof of employment at the travel agency following her discharge,
لإثبات العمل في وكالة السفر بعد تسريحها ،
I sent them all to you.
لقد أرسلتهم جميعًا إليك.
This claim about identity fraud is outrageous!
هذا الادعاء حول تزوير الهوية شائن!
[line beeps]
[أصوات خط]
The articles about Ms. Hong's identity fraud have been refuted.
تم دحض المقالات المتعلقة بالتزوير في هوية السيدة هونغ.
By any chance,
بأي فرصة،
is there anything else we should be aware of?
هل هناك أي شيء آخر يجب أن نكون على علم به؟
If there are any more issues about her--
إذا كانت هناك أية مشكلات أخرى عنها--
Sounds like you're assuming there will be more problems.
يبدو أنك تفترض أنه سيكون هناك المزيد من المشاكل.
Can you not handle situations like this?
لا يمكنك التعامل مع مثل هذه المواقف؟
Sir, your approval rating is plummeting at the moment.
سيدي ، معدل موافقتك ينخفض ​​في الوقت الحالي.
Han Kyungrok's team will strike even harder.
سيضرب فريق Han Kyungrok بقوة أكبر.
Do you want to lose in this game before we even hit the streets?
هل تريد أن تخسر في هذه اللعبة حتى قبل أن نصل إلى الشوارع؟
I will make sure you win the election, no matter what.
سوف أتأكد من فوزك في الانتخابات مهما حدث.
Not only for you, Candidate Pyo, but also for me.
ليس فقط من أجلك ، المرشح بيو ، ولكن أيضًا من أجلي.
If that's how you feel, I have nothing to worry about,
إذا كان هذا ما تشعر به ، فلا داعي للقلق ،
even if a bigger issue arises.
حتى لو ظهرت مشكلة أكبر.
Pardon?
عفو؟
Will 10 billion won be enough to deal with the press?
هل تكفي 10 مليارات وون للتعامل مع الصحافة؟
After all, doesn't money do the talking in election campaigns
بعد كل شيء ، لا يستخدم المال الكلام في الحملات الانتخابية
rather than the campaign manager's mouth?
بدلا من فم مدير الحملة؟
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخلوي]
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Pyo Jaehyun speaking.
بيو جيهيون يتحدث.
[Sangbae] Dojin asked me to run a background check on you.
[Sangbae] طلب مني Dojin إجراء فحص أمني لك.
Go for it. I've been waiting for this.
أذهب خلفها.  لقد كنت في انتظار هذا.
Guess it's my turn now.
أعتقد أنه دوري الآن.
INCOMING CALL UNCLE
وارد نداء العم
Uncle?
عم؟
010-0232-8459 UHM SANGBAE
010-0232-8459 UHM SANGBAE
Mr. Uhm?
سيد أوم؟
[stomps]
[يطأ]
[Jo] No. 91.
[انا لست.  91.
Did the director send you?
هل أرسل لك المدير؟
- Hmm? - [No. 91 screams]
- همم؟  - [لا.  91 صراخ]
[assassins grunting]
[قتلة شخير]
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Tell Director Kim
أخبر المدير كيم
that I'll be seeing her soon.
التي سأراها قريبًا.
You may go.
يمكنك الذهاب.
[rustling]
[سرقة]
I suppose Pyo Jaehyun…
أفترض بيو جيهيون ...
is done with me.
انتهى معي.
- [bangs] - What? You lost him?
- [غرة] - ماذا؟  هل فقدته؟
This makes me seem like a fool to Candidate Pyo!
هذا يجعلني أبدو كأنني أحمق للمرشح بيو!
[Seondeok] You want to see your sister?
[Seondeok] هل تريدين رؤية أختك؟
Then do as I say.
ثم افعل ما اقول.
This is all for your sister.
هذا كل شيء لأختك.
[No. 50] I thought you were dead.
[لا.  50] اعتقدت أنك ميت.
After you fell off my bike,
بعد أن سقطت من دراجتي ،
I fell off the cliff. Then I lost my memory.
لقد سقطت من الجرف.  ثم فقدت ذاكرتي.
Had I known you were at Hanwool, I would've gotten you out of there.
لو كنت أعرف أنك في Hanwool ، لكنت أخرجتك من هناك.
I would've never left you with her.
لم أكن لأتركك معها أبدًا.
Hey!
يا!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
That kind of violent behavior is unacceptable.
هذا النوع من السلوك العنيف غير مقبول.
Mr. Cha!
السيد.  أب!
How dare you shout while on duty?
كيف تجرؤ على الصراخ أثناء العمل؟
At the town house with children, huh?
في منزل المدينة مع الأطفال ، أليس كذلك؟
[Jiu] You want to die?
[جيو] تريد أن تموت؟
Why are you acting like you're his boss?
لماذا تتصرف وكأنك رئيسه؟
- Want me to bring my gun out again? - I wasn't acting like his boss!
- هل تريد مني إخراج بندقيتي مرة أخرى؟  - لم أكن أتصرف مثل رئيسه!
He was kicking the trash and screaming "Ah! Ah!"
كان يركل القمامة ويصرخ "آه! آه!"
Mr. Cha was being bad. Should he be paid to act like that?
كان السيد تشا سيئا.  هل يجب أن يدفع له ليعمل هكذا؟
My uncle's just a man. If something's bothering him, he can shout and get angry.
عمي مجرد رجل.  إذا كان هناك شيء يزعجه ، يمكنه الصراخ والغضب.
What's wrong with that?
ما الخطأ فى ذلك؟
And my uncle's super nice. I know him better than you.
وعمي لطيف للغاية.  أنا أعرفه أفضل منك.
I'm warning you, don't mess with me.
أنا أحذرك ، لا تعبث معي.
[Leo] Dang it, you. I'm telling my grandpa everything!
[ليو] دانغ ، أنت.  أنا أقول لجدي كل شيء!
Both of you, don't talk to me ever again!
كلاكما ، لا تتحدث إلي مرة أخرى!
Gosh.
يا الهي.
What? That brat.
ماذا؟  أن شقي.
Uncle, you okay?
العم ، هل أنت بخير؟
Just you wait. I need to finish this fight with my grumpy bestie.
فقط انتظر.  أنا بحاجة لإنهاء هذه المعركة مع صديقي الغاضب.
Jang Leo!
جانجليو!
[clapping]
[تصفيق]
[Jo] How touching.
[جو] كيف مؤثرة.
No. 50's daughter recognizes her own kin.
ابنة رقم 50 تتعرف على أقاربها.
She cares for her uncle quite deeply.
إنها تهتم بعمها بعمق.
I almost teared up a little.
كنت على وشك البكاء قليلا.
Watch what you say.
راقب ماتقول.
You shouldn't be wandering around.
لا يجب أن تتجول.
Why haven't you killed No. 50 yet?
لماذا لم تقتل رقم 50 بعد؟
Just say the word.
فقط قل الكلمة.
If you don't think you can do it,
إذا كنت تعتقد أنك لا تستطيع فعل ذلك ،
I'll kill her for you right now.
سأقتلها من أجلك الآن.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Don't tell me you're having doubts because she's blood.
لا تقل لي أن لديك شكوك لأنها دم.
Don't tell me you'll betray Mother Director?
لا تقل لي أنك ستخون الأم المديرة؟
[Jo chuckles] Tsk, tsk, tsk.
[جو يضحك] تسك ، تسك ، تسك.
You really shouldn't bite the hand that feeds you.
لا يجب أن تعض اليد التي تطعمك.
- I said watch what you say! - I saw you hesitate.
- قلت شاهد ما تقوله!  - رأيتك تتردد.
I told you to never let your enemy know your next move.
أخبرتك ألا تدع عدوك يعرف خطوتك التالية.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
all I've been thinking about lately is how I'm going to kill that bitch No. 50…
كل ما كنت أفكر فيه مؤخرًا هو كيف سأقتل تلك العاهرة رقم 50 ...
and how to make it for a wife of a famous household
وكيف تصنعه لزوجة منزل مشهور
as terrible and horrific as possible.
فظيع ومرعب قدر الإمكان.
Thinking about it
افكر في الأمر
has made my life quite enjoyable.
جعلت حياتي ممتعة للغاية.
Improves my appetite too.
يحسن شهيتي أيضا.
[thuds]
[جلجل]
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
He's conscious, but why can't he talk?
إنه واع ، لكن لماذا لا يتكلم؟
Is he a living corpse?
هل هو جثة حية؟
Kyojin!
كيوجين!
Shit.
القرف.
Huh?
هاه؟
Who the hell is this guy?
من هم الجحيم هو هذا الرجل؟
It's been a while, Chairman.
لقد مرت فترة من الوقت ، أيها الرئيس.
What the hell brings you here? [chuckles]
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا بحق الجحيم؟  [ضحكات خافتة]
My goodness.
رباه.
Your face looks even more worn than my old, wrinkly face.
يبدو وجهك أكثر تآكلًا من وجهي القديم المتجعد.
Weren't you pointing fingers at me, as if I'd done something to Ko Taesun?
ألم تكن توجه أصابع الاتهام إلي ، كما لو كنت قد فعلت شيئًا لكو تايسون؟
Oh, right.
صحيح.
I hear your wife's an assassin, something or other?
سمعت أن زوجتك قاتلة ، شيء أو آخر؟
She must be causing you so much grief.
لابد أنها تسبب لك الكثير من الحزن.
I'm a presidential candidate.
أنا مرشح رئاسي.
I'm being vetted as the nation's strictest and fairest figure,
يتم فحصي كأكثر شخصية صرامة وعدالة في البلاد ،
so don't you worry about me.
لذلك لا تقلق علي.
Instead, shall we take a trip down memory lane?
بدلاً من ذلك ، هل يجب أن نقوم برحلة في حارة الذاكرة؟
I figure you'll also find it quite interesting, Chairman.
أعتقد أنك ستجده أيضًا مثيرًا للاهتمام ، رئيس.
Here are some files on Pyo Jaehyun that we have at Kumjo.
هذه بعض الملفات الموجودة على Pyo Jaehyun التي لدينا في Kumjo.
I'm sure you'll find what you need in there.
أنا متأكد من أنك ستجد ما تحتاجه هناك.
- Thank you, Mr. Uhm. - We appreciate this.
- شكرا لك سيد أوم.  - نحن نقدر هذا.
[paper rustles]
[حفيف ورق]
[Jaehyun] Do you remember Dr. Kim Sohye?
[جيهيون] هل تتذكر الدكتور كيم سوهي؟
Dr. Kim Sohye ran a small private clinic in Samcheok.
كان الدكتور كيم Sohye يدير عيادة خاصة صغيرة في Samcheok.
Who?
من؟
And what about ammothamnine?
وماذا عن الأموثامينين؟
Treatment for cranial nerve disorders that you sold to a foreign company
علاج اضطرابات العصب القحفي الذي قمت ببيعه لشركة أجنبية
about 20 years ago.
منذ حوالي 20 عامًا.
You stole the technology from Dr. Kim and killed her.
لقد سرقت التكنولوجيا من دكتور كيم وقتلتها.
I'm sure you remember this.
أنا متأكد من أنك تتذكر هذا.
[Jaehyun] Mom.
[جيهيون] أمي.
[whimpers]
[أنين]
[both panting]
[كلاهما يلهث]
[tires squeal]
[صرير الإطارات]
[Sohye] Oh, no!
[Sohye] أوه ، لا!
[line ringing]
[رنين خط]
It's taken care of, Chairman.
لقد تم الاعتناء به ، أيها الرئيس.
I've secured Dr. Kim's research files.
لقد قمت بتأمين ملفات أبحاث الدكتور كيم.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
[Dojin] Dr. Kim Sohye, a research director,
[دوجين] الدكتور كيم سوهي ، مدير الأبحاث ،
developed a treatment for dementia for a large corporation.
طور علاجًا للخرف لشركة كبيرة.
She was found to have pocketed the research funds.
تبين أنها استولت على أموال البحث.
When the truth came out, Dr. Kim stole the research files and fled.
عندما ظهرت الحقيقة ، سرق الدكتور كيم ملفات البحث وهرب.
She caused a car crash while driving drunk and died instantly,
تسببت في حادث سيارة أثناء القيادة مخموراً وتوفيت على الفور ،
so did the passengers in the other vehicle.
وكذلك فعل ركاب السيارة الأخرى.
[Haesoo gasps]
[شهقات Haesoo]
So he kept it all hidden for a reason.
لذلك أبقى كل شيء مخفيًا لسبب ما.
Jaehyun couldn't talk about his mother.
لم يستطع Jaehyun التحدث عن والدته.
It says the research was funded by Kumjo Pharmaceuticals,
تقول أن البحث تم تمويله من قبل Kumjo Pharmaceuticals ،
but why did Father never mention this before?
لكن لماذا لم يذكر الأب هذا من قبل؟
He was probably waiting for the right timing.
ربما كان ينتظر التوقيت المناسب.
Maybe he was waiting to bring it up just before the election.
ربما كان ينتظر طرحها قبل الانتخابات مباشرة.
Clearly, Jaehyun was holding a grudge, and that's why he approached you and Kyojin.
من الواضح أن جيهيون كان يحمل ضغينة ، ولهذا اقترب منك ومن كيوجين.
Holding a grudge for what?
يحمل ضغينة من أجل ماذا؟
According to this article, his mother's at fault.
وفقًا لهذا المقال ، فإن والدته هي المخطئة.
It's probably misguided vengeance.
ربما يكون انتقامًا مضللًا.
After the accident, he dropped out of SNU Medicine and transferred to KAIST.
بعد الحادث ، ترك جامعة SNU Medicine وانتقل إلى KAIST.
Getting you kicked out of Hatch was all a part of his plan.
كان طردك من هاتش جزءًا من خطته.
[bell dings]
[قرع الجرس]
It's Mr. Park. I asked him for a favor.
إنه السيد بارك.  طلبت منه خدمة.
[Haesoo] Did you go to Samcheok?
[Haesoo] هل ذهبت إلى Samcheok؟
Did you get to meet any of Dr. Kim's coworkers?
هل قابلت أيًا من زملاء دكتور كيم في العمل؟
I got in touch with one of her colleagues.
لقد تواصلت مع أحد زملائها.
She said Dr. Kim conducted illegal human trials on her own patients at the clinic
وقالت إن الدكتورة كيم أجرت تجارب بشرية غير قانونية على مرضاها في العيادة
in the name of research.
باسم البحث.
By force?
بالقوة؟
Without the patient or guardian's consent?
بدون موافقة المريض أو ولي الأمر؟
Several patients died during the research,
مات العديد من المرضى خلال البحث ،
but it was swept under the rug after she died.
لكنها جرفت تحت البساط بعد وفاتها.
All the details are in here.
كل التفاصيل هنا.
Wait. What are you going to do?
انتظر.  ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟
This is enough to make Jaehyun lose the election.
هذا يكفي لجعل جيهيون يخسر الانتخابات.
You're going to do it? We're not exactly media darlings right now.
ستفعل ذلك؟  نحن لسنا بالضبط أعزاء وسائل الإعلام في الوقت الحالي.
Why wouldn't I? He's a presidential candidate, isn't he?
لماذا لا؟  إنه مرشح رئاسي ، أليس كذلك؟
Stop talking nonsense!
توقف عن الكلام هراء!
I've never put out a hit on anyone.
لم أقم أبدًا بضربة على أي شخص.
I don't know what you've heard,
لا اعرف ماذا سمعت
but her death has nothing to do with me.
ولكن موتها لا علاقة له بي.
You think there's no evidence that proves you ordered Dr. Kim
تعتقد أنه لا يوجد دليل يثبت أنك طلبت دكتور كيم
to conduct illegal human trials?
لإجراء محاكمات بشرية غير قانونية؟
My poor mother…
أمي المسكينة ...
was framed for all your bullshit and wrongfully murdered.
تم تأطيره على الرغم من كل هرائك وقتل ظلما.
You remember that?
تذكر ذاك؟
M-- Mother?
م - الأم؟
That's right.
صحيح.
The person in the passenger seat next to Dr. Kim on that night of the accident,
الشخص الجالس في مقعد الراكب المجاور للدكتور كيم في تلك الليلة من الحادث ،
her one and only son who survived the crash and got away,
ابنها الوحيد الذي نجا من الحادث وهرب ،
is standing before you now.
يقف أمامك الآن.
Evidence that you gave orders to Mr. Uhm and the truth about that accident,
دليل على أنك أعطيت الأوامر للسيد أوم والحقيقة بشأن ذلك الحادث ،
I have it all. Got it?
لدي كل شيء.  فهمتها؟
But here you are, shameless.
لكن ها أنت ، وقح.
Going on about how you're an honest businessman.
هل أنت رجل أعمال نزيه؟
COMMEMORATIVE MEDAL CHAIRMAN JANG KUMMO
رئيس ميدالية تذكارية جانغ كومو
I find it hilarious.
أجدها مضحكة.
[Kummo gasping]
[كومو يلهث]
Oh, that's right.
هذا صحيح.
Why would it be a big deal that you killed a doctor from the suburbs?
لماذا يكون قتل طبيب من الضواحي مشكلة كبيرة؟
You hired an assassin to take out the president of this nation…
لقد استأجرت قاتلًا لتطيح برئيس هذه الأمة ...
at his inaugural ceremony.
في حفل الافتتاح.
No, no.
لا لا.
I swear it wasn't me.
أقسم أنه لم يكن أنا.
I…
أنا…
I-- It's… It's all a misunderstanding.
أنا - إنه ... كل هذا سوء فهم.
[Jaehyun] Oh.
[جيهيون] أوه.
This is no time for a stroke, Chairman.
هذا ليس وقت السكتة الدماغية ، سيدي الرئيس.
Your son and his wife are looking into this case, as we speak.
ابنك وزوجته يبحثان في هذه القضية ، ونحن نتحدث.
They might discover your true colors.
قد يكتشفون ألوانك الحقيقية.
You okay with that?
هل أنت بخير مع ذلك؟
You-- You… How…
أنت - أنت ... كيف ...
If you want to keep your filthy secrets from the world…
إذا كنت تريد إخفاء أسرارك القذرة من العالم ...
you better stop your son and his wife yourself.
من الأفضل أن توقف ابنك وزوجته بنفسك.
I'll be watching
سأكون مشاهدة
to see how you decide to cover up your sins.
لترى كيف تقرر التستر على خطاياك.
[Kummo] You fucking bastard.
[كومو] أيها الوغد اللعين.
Why, I ought to--
لماذا يجب أن--
[Kummo groans]
[يئن كومو]
[Kummo gasping]
[كومو يلهث]
His health must be failing. Take him to a hospital quickly.
يجب أن تكون صحته فاشلة.  خذه إلى المستشفى بسرعة.
[Sangbae] Chairman!
[Sangbae] الرئيس!
- Get Dr. Choi on the phone now! - [assistant] Yes, sir.
- احصل على دكتور تشوي على الهاتف الآن!  - [المساعد] نعم سيدي.
[Kummo sighs]
[يتنهد كومو]
Chairman!
رئيس!
The researcher who pocketed
الباحث الذي دخل في جيوبه
the funds that Kumjo Pharmaceuticals generously provided at the time
الأموال التي قدمتها شركة Kumjo Pharmaceuticals بسخاء في ذلك الوقت
is none other than Candidate Pyo's mother!
ليست سوى والدة المرشح بيو!
When the truth was revealed, she took the research files and ran off into night.
عندما تم الكشف عن الحقيقة ، أخذت ملفات البحث وهربت في الليل.
On top of that, she was driving under the influence of alcohol.
علاوة على ذلك ، كانت تقود سيارتها تحت تأثير الكحول.
But the person who accompanied her while she was on the run was Candidate Pyo!
لكن الشخص الذي رافقها أثناء هروبها كان المرشح بيو!
How will a presidential candidate with such moral issues
كيف سيكون مرشح رئاسي مع مثل هذه القضايا الأخلاقية
be able to govern a nation?
تكون قادرة على حكم أمة؟
He has covered up the evil sins committed by his mother
قد تستر على خطايا أمه
and has encouraged his wife to lie.
وشجع زوجته على الكذب.
Such are the true colors of Candidate Pyo Jaehyun!
هذه هي الألوان الحقيقية للمرشح بيو جيهيون!
[shutters clicking]
[نقر مصاريع]
It's perfect. His ratings will go up by 10%.
انها مثالية.  سترتفع تقييماته بنسبة 10٪.
They say help comes from unexpected places,
يقولون المساعدة تأتي من أماكن غير متوقعة ،
but who knew it would be Anchorwoman Ko?
ولكن من كان يعلم أنها ستكون Anchorwoman Ko؟
We got Candidate Pyo real good this time.
لقد حصلنا على المرشح بيو جيدًا هذه المرة.
Did you really approach Kyojin and me to get revenge?
هل حقًا اقتربت مني وأنا كيوجين للانتقام؟
Kyojin's accident…
حادث كيوجين ...
was you?
كان أنت؟
[cell phone vibrates]
[يهتز الهاتف الخلوي]
Yes.
نعم.
There's one thing I failed to mention.
هناك شيء واحد لم أذكره.
The chairman had Pyo's mother killed in the accident.
قتل الرئيس والدة بيو في الحادث.
If that gets out, Kumjo will never recover.
إذا حدث ذلك ، فلن يتعافى Kumjo أبدًا.
What on earth are you saying?
ماذا تقول بحق السماء؟
[knocks]
[يقرع]
[line beeps]
[أصوات خط]
Han's press conference is over.
انتهى مؤتمر هان الصحفي.
Jaehyun won't be able to counter this so easily.
لن يكون Jaehyun قادرًا على مواجهة هذا بهذه السهولة.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
ما هو الخطأ؟  هل حدث شئ؟
You lost Mr. Jo?
هل فقدت السيد جو؟
[Seondeok] I take full responsibility.
- أنا أتحمل كامل المسؤولية.
How can I hand Hatch over to someone of such incompetence?
كيف يمكنني تسليم هاتش لشخص غير كفء؟
[paper rustles]
[حفيف ورق]
Manhwe Group's Chairman Song Juman,
رئيس مجلس إدارة مجموعة مانهوي سونغ جومان ،
Han Kyungrok's campaign sponsor.
راعي حملة هان كيونغروك.
Han's funds need to run dry for us to hit the brakes on KDP's rise.
تحتاج أموال هان إلى النفاد حتى نضغط على الفرامل مع صعود الحزب الديمقراطي الكردستاني.
Please give me a chance to prove myself and make up for my failure with Mr. Jo.
من فضلك أعطني فرصة لإثبات نفسي وتعويض فشلي مع السيد جو.
Our ace is already prepared and on standby.
تم إعداد الآس لدينا بالفعل وعلى أهبة الاستعداد.
Your ace?
الآص الخاص بك؟
Are you talking about Mr. Cha?
هل تتحدث عن السيد تشا؟
What does everyone call Pilseung here?
ماذا يسمي الجميع بيلسونغ هنا؟
I know he's Taera's brother.
أعلم أنه شقيق تيرا.
I've already run a DNA test.
لقد أجريت بالفعل اختبار الحمض النووي.
Shall we…
هلا فعلنا…
test his skills then?
اختبر مهاراته بعد ذلك؟
[No. 105] Yes.
[لا.  105] نعم.
I'll take care of it tonight,
سأعتني بها الليلة ،
Mother Director.
الأم المخرجة.
As of today, it's been decided. The Blue House goes to Chairman Han.
اعتبارًا من اليوم ، تم تحديد ذلك.  البيت الأزرق يذهب إلى الرئيس هان.
Chairman Song, we haven't even officially begun campaigning yet.
الرئيس سونغ ، لم نبدأ حتى الآن في الحملة بشكل رسمي.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
If Pyo heard you, he'd be so sad, seriously.
إذا سمعك بيو ، فسيكون حزينًا جدًا ، بجدية.
He can be sad all he wants.
يمكن أن يكون حزينا كل ما يريد.
How could he serve the nation as a man of such pathetic character?
كيف يمكن أن يخدم الأمة كرجل في مثل هذه الشخصية المثيرة للشفقة؟
That boy is still wet behind the ears.
هذا الصبي لا يزال مبتلًا خلف أذنيه.
He should be thanking us for even dealing with him.
ينبغي أن يشكرنا حتى على التعامل معه.
Am I not right?
ألست على حق؟
I think you may be right.
اظن انك ممكن ان تكون محق.
Here's to--
هنا ل--
Manhwe Group's sole bet is on KDP and Han Kyungrok.
الرهان الوحيد لمجموعة Manhwe Group هو على KDP و Han Kyungrok.
You know that, right?
انت تعلم ذلك صحيح؟
[Chairman Song] We are in this together, until the end.
[رئيس أغنية] نحن في هذا معا ، حتى النهاية.
Of course. Of course, let's ch-- cheers.
بالطبع.  بالطبع ، دعنا نخبرك.
I'll drink to that, Chairman Song.
سأشرب لذلك ، الرئيس سونغ.
[Chairman Song laughing]
[رئيس سونغ يضحك]
[Kyungrok singing "When You and I Were Young, Maggie"]
[كيونغروك يغني "عندما كنا صغيرين ، ماجي"]
My men will be loading hefty presents for you.
سيحمل رجالي هدايا ضخمة من أجلك.
You may find the way back to be a little "weighty."
قد تجد طريق العودة لتكون "ثقيل الوزن" قليلاً.
I hope that's okay!
آمل أن يكون هذا جيدًا!
[both laughing]
[كلاهما يضحك]
[Kyungrok] Oh-- Oh, my!
[Kyungrok] أوه - أوه ، يا إلهي!
[No. 50] No!
[لا.  50] لا!
Hajun.
الرائحة.
Put the gun down.
ضع المسدس ارضا.
Please stop, Hajun.
من فضلك توقف يا هاجون.
Hajun, please stop. Please-- No!
هاجون ، توقف من فضلك.  من فضلك لا!
- [thuds] - [Chairman Song gasps]
- [جلخ] - [الرئيس سونغ يلهث]
Oh-- Oh, my! Chairman Song, wake up. Hey, what are you doing?
أوه - أوه ، يا!  الرئيس سونغ ، استيقظ.  مرحبا ماذا تفعل؟
- Do something! - [bodyguard] Chairman Song!
- قم بعمل ما!  - [حارس] رئيس سونغ!
- [Kyungrok] Call an ambulance! - [bodyguard 2] Chairman!
- [Kyungrok] اتصل بسيارة إسعاف!  - [حارس 2] رئيس!
[bodyguard 3] He's not breathing!
[حارس 3] إنه لا يتنفس!
I told you not to shoot.
قلت لك لا تطلق النار.
Why'd you do it? Why?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟  لماذا؟
Because it's my job.
لأنه وظيفتي.
Because if Mother Director gives the order, I have to do it,
لأنه إذا أعطت الأم المديرة الأمر ، يجب أن أفعل ذلك ،
whether it was 15 years ago or now.
سواء كان ذلك قبل 15 عامًا أو الآن.
[applause]
[تصفيق]
[gunshot]
[طلق ناري]
[clamoring]
[صراخ]
[Seondeok] You want to see your sister?
[Seondeok] هل تريدين رؤية أختك؟
Then do as I say.
ثم افعل ما اقول.
This is all for your sister,
هذا كل شيء لأختك ،
No. 105.
رقم 105.
It wasn't you.
لم تكن أنت.
It's not your fault.
انها ليست غلطتك.
[No. 50 cries]
[لا.  50 صرخات]
PANDORA: BENEATH THE PARADISE
باندورا: بينية الجنة
[Jaehyun] Cha Pilseung. Can we trust him?
[جيهيون] تشا بيلسونغ.  هل يمكننا الوثوق به؟
Nevertheless, he is still Taera's brother.
ومع ذلك ، فهو لا يزال شقيق طيرة.
[Kummo] If you delve deeper into this with Ms. Ko, it'll put Kumjo at risk.
[كومو] إذا تعمقت في هذا الأمر مع السيدة كو ، فسوف يعرض ذلك كومجو للخطر.
What did he just say?
ماذا قال لتوه؟
[Dojin] How can I look my wife in the eyes now?
[Dojin] كيف يمكنني أن أنظر في عيني زوجتي الآن؟
How can you be so cruel to that poor woman?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون بهذه القسوة مع تلك المرأة المسكينة؟
The next leader of Hatch is you, Koo Sungchan.
زعيم هاتش القادم هو أنت ، كو سونغشان.
Let's show them who you are, yeah?
دعنا نريهم من أنت ، أجل؟
- [blows landing] - [grunting]
- [ضربات الهبوط] - [الشخير]
[No. 50] The one behind it all…
[لا.  50] الشخص الذي يقف وراء كل ذلك ...
is you?
هل أنت؟
[Jaehyun] You hiding something?
[جاهيون] هل تخفي شيئًا؟
Ripped and synced by TTEOKBOKKIsubs
ممزق ومزامنة بواسطة TTEOKBOKKIsubs